For those of you who use Claude Code regularly, you probably already know this.
Claude Code is already incredibly powerful.
It can read code, run commands, and call all sorts of tools.
It can even understand screenshots we throw at it, no problem.
But right now, it has two main limitations.
First, its knowledge is limited to the information it was trained on.
So when we ask it about recent events, it often can't answer.
Second, its outputs are limited to text and code.
like generating images or creating videos.
or even speak and generate voice.
It can't do any of that.
So, to address Claude Code's shortcomings,
So, in this video, let's put it to the test.
So, can we solve all these limitations with just a single command?
So, to address Claude Code's shortcomings,
It's super simple.
And all we need is one tool.
This tool is called the Model Studio CLI.
The installation is super simple.
All we have to do is copy the prompt provided by the official documentation.
Now, let's go back to Claude Code.
And then we'll just paste in the prompt we just copied.
and have it read the installation documentation.
and install the Alibaba Cloud Model Studio CLI for me according to the instructions.
And just like that, we run it, and Claude Code will automatically install it for us.
Model Studio CLI
so we don't have to install it manually.
Here, it says the installation is complete and has been verified.
Alright, all we need to do now is provide it with the API key.
All we need to do is go to the Alibaba Cloud Model Studio console.
and get an API Key.
and provide the API Key to Claude Code.
And we're all set to go.
I'll drop the registration link in the comments section.
New users get a free quota.
You can follow along with the video as we go.
Then, click on the 'Create API Key' button in the top-right corner.
Alright, let's head back to Claude Code.
We'll just tell it in plain English: "configure my API Key."
Then, just paste the API Key we just created and copied, and Claude Code will automatically set it up for us.
and Claude Code will automatically set it up for us.
Once it's installed,
And just like that, Claude Code has a whole new set of capabilities.
This includes online searches, accessing knowledge bases, and memory banks.
image generation and editing,
video generation, text-to-speech, and speech recognition.
It can also call upon the workflows and Agents we've already set up on Alibaba Cloud Model Studio.
Alright, let's put it to the test in Claude Code.
So, first, let's tackle the first limitation of Claude Code.
and give it the ability to get real-time information.
In other words, we're giving it access to the latest and greatest knowledge out there.
Now, before we install it,
We asked it about a recent event.
As you can see, it either doesn't know,
or the answer is outdated.
So, for the question we just asked,
We can continue testing this out in Claude Code.
You can directly use the slash command plus the Bailian CLI.
After that, we can just describe our task in natural language.
the version number of the latest AutoGen agent.
and the major updates.
And then just send it.
So, with a prompt like this,
Claude Code will then use the Model Studio CLI
to search for this Agent for us.
and the version number of its latest release.
and the main updates.
And there it is. It's found the version number for the AutoGen Agent.
Now, if you don't want to use the slash commands,
You can also just tell it in plain English.
invoke the Bailian CLI to search for the version number of this Agent.
And there's a major update.
And just like that, it will call the Bailian CLI to perform the search.
And just like that,
This gives Claude Code much more powerful web search capabilities.
This allows it to perform real-time internet searches.
So, after installing the Model Studio CLI for Claude Code,
But it's not just about searching.
and connect to knowledge bases.
Let's start by testing out its memory bank.
For example, I'll type in the prompt: 'Please remember...'
My tech stack is Swift.
And then, just send it.
And right here, it's telling me that it will be stored in the default memory bank of Model Studio.
And then we can see that it's calling the Model Studio CLI.
And here, it shows that the data has been successfully saved to the default Bailian memory bank.
Alright, let's head back to the Model Studio console and check it out.
Let's click on this memory bank.
And under Memory Details, we can go ahead and click to view it.
And right here, it's stored the tech stack that we just told it about.
And you can see the update time here is just a moment ago.
So, with something like this,
we can then directly use Model Studio.
Its memory bank serves as the long-term memory system for our Claude Code.
Even if we switch devices,
and sync the memory to the new device as well.
Plus, it also supports a knowledge base.
So for the Knowledge Base, we'll just click 'Enable Now and Create'.
And right here, we can set the name for our knowledge base.
For instance, the knowledge base I'm creating here, I'll name it 'Harness Engineering'.
I'll upload a document related to Harness.
And then, click Next.
And here, it shows that the file is being parsed.
Alright, now let's test out the knowledge base we just built, right here in Claude Code.
and have it use this knowledge base to retrieve information.
The prompt I'm using is to search for information within the Harness project.
an introduction to Harness.
And then, we just send it.
And right here, it's telling us that it's going to call the Bailian CLI to perform the search.
So, it's pulling from the knowledge base we just created.
and retrieved all these introductions related to Harness.
And the results it retrieved are incredibly detailed.
So, we won't go through all the details here.
And just like that,
And just like that, we've given our Claude Code an external knowledge base.
So now we have a knowledge base and a memory bank.
Over time, this will build up our own knowledge flywheel.
Alright, next up, let's tackle the second limitation of Claude Code.
enabling it to generate images and videos.
So, right here in Claude Code, I can just type in a natural language description.
Let's have it generate a set of main images for an Amazon e-commerce listing.
I'm asking for six images.
The product is a solid black, men's summer T-shirt.
Alright, let's just send it. And here it says it's generating 6 images.
So what it's using right now is the image generation capability from Alibaba Cloud Model Studio.
Qwen-Image 2.0.
And it supports multiple sizes.
And it's already prompting me here.
And it's done. Six high-quality main images for an Amazon listing.
Alright, let's open them up and take a look.
Alright, let's start with the first image.
This is a black T-shirt.
This style is a perfect fit for e-commerce product images.
And here's the second image.
As you can see, the result is pretty good too.
Alright, let's take a look at the third one.
This is also a close-up of the T-shirt's material.
And this is the fourth one.
So, with that in mind,
With the power of Alibaba Cloud's Model Studio,
our Claude Code can now generate images.
And it's not just about generating images.
It can also edit those images.
For example, let's have it add a logo to this T-shirt.
So, I'll just type in the prompt.
Add a nice logo to the T-shirt in the first image.
And then, just send it.
So, with a command like this,
And it will call upon the image editing capabilities of Alibaba Cloud's Model Studio.
It supports modifications,
as well as merging multiple images and more.
And here it says the logo has been added.
We can click to check it out.
As you can see, it's added a white logo to the T-shirt.
The result is actually pretty good.
Alright, next up, let's test out its video generation capabilities.
Let's test its video generation capabilities.
So, we can go ahead and pick one.
the image that the Bailian CLI just generated for us.
So, let's just go with this image, for example.
And now, I'll just type in the prompt.
and have it use this image as a reference.
Generate a video that's about 5 seconds long.
And just send it.
First, it will read the image we've told it to reference.
And then it will call the video generation model.
Specifically, the HappyHorse 1.0 model.
and generate a video for us from the image.
And here it tells us the video has been generated.
Let's find the video.
And then, let's hit play.
As you can see, the video turned out incredibly well.
It even generated background music for the video.
And the character in the video, their movements are incredibly smooth.
Even the leaves in the background are swaying in the breeze.
Everything looks incredibly realistic.
And the person's facial expressions look incredibly realistic, too.
We can even modify the video it generates.
All we need to do is follow the prompts from Claude Code.
and have it edit the video for us.
For instance, we can add action shots from different angles.
add text subtitles,
and even different background scenes.
longer video versions, and so on.
Next up, we can also address the third shortcoming of Claude Code.
Which is the voice feature.
With the power of the Bailian CLI,
This means Claude Code now has text-to-speech capabilities.
and even recognize speech.
In other words, it can both speak and listen.
Alright, let's start by testing out the BaiLian CLI.
Now, let's talk about the speech generation capabilities of the Bailian CLI.
So, in Claude Code,
I'll use a slash command to call the BAILIAN CLI.
Now, let's have it generate an audio reading.
the following poem.
And after that, we'll give it a poem.
The poem is "Farewell to Cambridge Again."
And it says here that the generation was successful.
and it's been saved to this location.
And it notes that the voice is gentle and delicate.
Alright, let's open it up and hear how it sounds.
Quietly I leave,
As I came quietly.
I gently wave my hand,
To bid farewell to the clouds in the Western Paradise.
The golden willows by the riverbank are brides in the setting sun.
The gorgeous reflection in the sparkling waves sways in my heart.
The green weeds on the soft mud,
are swaying in the gentle waves;
In the gentle ripples of the River Cam,
I would be a waterweed.
That pool under the elm's shade is not a clear spring,
It's a rainbow in the sky.
Crushed and scattered among the floating algae.
To save some time,
So, let's just listen to the first few seconds here.
And the audio it generates? The quality is seriously impressive.
And the voice is so gentle and delicate.
When it's reading this poem,
Both the pacing and the emotion...
all perfectly match the mood of the poem.
So, with that in place,
And just like that, our Claude Code now has text-to-speech capabilities.
Alright, next up, let's test out its speech recognition capabilities.
So, it can listen. I've prepared a piece of audio for this.
Let's have a listen first.
The evening wind drifts past the old street corner,
and gently swaying the shadows of the lights.
Someone turns back at dusk,
Like recalling a name, left half-spoken.
So, in Claude Code, I'll just type in the command to transcribe this audio.
and then follow it with the path to the audio file.
And then, we'll just send it.
And just like that, it successfully converted the audio into text.
Let's take a look.
And the text it recognized is perfectly accurate.
And on top of that, it even recognized this as a very beautiful piece of poetry.
This gives our Claude Code the ability to listen,
and the ability to speak.
Alright, so everything we've tested so far has been the model's own capabilities.
Model Studio also allows Claude Code to call upon
applications that we've already set up on the Bailian platform.
So, over here in the application management section of Model Studio,
I've created an application here that can scrape the latest AI news.
And then, we can directly call this application right within Claude Code.
to fetch the AI news.
The prompt I'm using is simply to call the AI news application.
to get the latest AI news for today.
And now, we'll just send it right here.
And just like that, it's searched for and found the latest AI-related news for today.
So we won't go through all the details here.
So, with that done,
And just like that, we've finished building an application on Alibaba Cloud Model Studio.
And then, directly within Claude Code, we can call the application we just built.
to get our tasks done.
and give Claude Code even more capabilities.
So far, we've only been testing the individual capabilities of the Bailian CLI.
And now, for the main event.
We're going to have Claude Code string all these capabilities of the Bailian CLI together.
So, for instance, let's try a more complex, multi-step task here.
So, the prompt I'm talking about is this:
Search for which open-source AI project is trending this week.
Pick one and create an introductory image for it.
And then, generate a 15-second preview video.
And finally, let's add a Chinese voice-over.
And then, we just send it.
And with that, we can just let it run.
The key to this task is Claude Code.
It will be responsible for figuring out the steps,
and what order to call them in.
And the Bailian CLI will act as its cognitive and generative backend.
and actually execute each step.
So, with that in place,
You can just use a single sentence in natural language,
to have your own AI agent
accomplish complex tasks that previously required multiple tools to complete.
And right here, you can see it. The prompt says the introductory image has been generated.
And now, it's generating the video.
And now it's telling us the voice-over has been generated as well.
And it's done. The video is now being generated.
So, as we've seen from the hands-on tests in this video,
Before installing the Bailian CLI,
Claude Code is limited to information from the past.
and could only output text and code.
But after installing the Bailian CLI,
It can search the internet,
and have long-term memory.
It can search knowledge bases,
It can generate images,
generate videos,
And it can even talk.
And it can even understand speech.
It can also call upon the applications we've already built on the Alibaba Cloud Model Studio platform.
It can even orchestrate its own applications.
And the best part? You can get all of this with just a single command.
So, if you'd also like to unlock these capabilities for your own AI or Agent,
I'll put the registration link for the Model Studio CLI in the comment section.
I've put the link in the comments section.
New users get a free quota.
So, it's first come, first served.
Also, if you want to stay updated on the latest developments for Bailian CLI,
You can search for Model Studio AI on GitHub.
This organization hosts the Model Studio CLI.
There are also some skills that can help the CLI run even better.
Model Studio will also continue to work with experts in the field of AI,
and developers to build together.
We're also looking forward to your support and engagement.
And that's all for this video.
Please feel free to like, follow, and share this video.
Thanks for watching.